<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Walk About</string>
    <string name="StartRoute">Start the route</string>
    <string name="infoApp">Walk About is an application developed for the tourist office. With this app, the user can choose a route in Breda and follow it led by the app.</string>
    <string name="InfoColourblind">The application can also be used for people with color blindness.</string>
    <string name="kleurenblindheid">Color blindness</string>
    <string name="medemogelijk">Made possible by AGS.</string>
    <string name="last_loc_not_found">Last location not available…</string>
    <string name="no_loc_permissions">No location permissions granted, the route cannot work without location access!</string>
    <string name="route_in_progress">Do you want to continue with your previous route?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
	<string name="skip_point">Skip this point</string>
	<string name="visited_already">Visited</string>

    <string name="blind_walls_description">
        Together with the municipality and property owners,
        the Blind Walls Gallery invites international graphic designers, street artists, typographers
        and illustrators to update the image of the city.\n\n
        Since 2014, the Blind Walls Gallery changes the appearance of Breda through impressive and
        meaningful murals inspired by local heritage and stories.
    </string>

    <string name="historic_kilometer_title">Historic Kilometer</string>
    <string name="historic_kilometer_description">
        With this tour, we present you with the oldest part of the city Breda.
        The tour will guide you amongst the most historically-important sights.
        But also more recent additions are not forgotten, as for example the Chassé Theater will be visited.
        Some buildings have such a big history that the tour guide can\'t say every detail.
        Therefore, the app presents you with written, detailed information that can be read
        whenever it suits you. This way we try to make Historic Kilometer appealing for everyone.
    </string>
</resources>